Yves: Ah, hey~
Yves: It's Yves, the special MC for LOOΠΔ / ODD EYE CIRCLE~
Yves: Making the audience laugh is my mission~
Yves: I'll try my best!
Kim Lip: I will appear as the special MC!
Kim Lip: And LOOΠΔ 1/3 is performing a song called '지금 더 좋아해'
Kim Lip: I'm waiting for my turn to appear on the stage!
Kim Lip: Cheer up, LOOΠΔ 1/3!!
Choerry: YeoJin has never done any performance on a stage before~
Choerry: Watching that she's doing really hard like this makes me feel great and~
Choerry: I almost feel like her mom~
Choerry: Please film her now~~
HeeJin: It's so hectic~
HeeJin: I'll do my best to host as the special MC for LOOΠΔ / yyxy
(Practice on pronunciation of LOOΠΔ / yyxy)
HeeJin: Y Y X Y
(And Yves, Kim Lip, Choerry, and HeeJin did really well as the special MC!)